Guide to the All of the Above records, [2005]-2020. UA.31.07.0007
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
All of the Above records
[2005]-2020
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
All of the Above (Durham, NC)
UA.31.07.0007
0.5 Linear Feet
13.2 Gigabytes
All of the Above (AOTA) is an annual theatrical production comprised of monologues written, performed by, and directed by Duke women about Duke life. The All of the Above records contain programs, scripts, list of participants, a directors manual titled "Making all of the Above," and two mini DV digital videocassettes of the 2008 production.
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The All of the Above records were received by the University Archives as a transfer prior to 2008 and in 2008, 2014, 2016, 2017, and 2020.
Historical Note
All of the Above (AOTA) is an annual theatrical production comprised of monologues written, performed by, and directed by Duke women about Duke life. AOTA's goal is to present a collection of women's voices that will spark honest dialogue about serious issues, such as rape, eating disorders, success, and relationships. AOTA was developed and executed by senior Mary Adkins in 2003 as a response to the 2003 Women's Initiative commissioned by then President Nannerl O. Keohane. The first production took place in April 2004.
Collection Overview
The All of the Above records contain programs, scripts, list of participants, a directors manual titled "Making all of the Above," and two mini DV digital videocassettes of the 2008 production. In 2019, All of the Above began including digital video files of the performances.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection contains electronic records that must be requested and accessed in our reading room. Contact Research Services with questions.
Mini-DV; Women -- Sexual behavior -- Drama; Self-esteem in women -- Drama; Monologues; Body image in women -- Drama; All of the Above (Durham, NC)
- All of the Above records, 2005-2020
  - All of the Above [2005] Production (Box 1)
  - All of the Above 2006 Production (Box 1)
  - All of the Above 2007 Production (Box 1)
  - Make All of the Above, A Director's Manual, Created Spring 2008 (Box 1)
  - All of the Above 2008 Production (Box 1)
  - All of the Above 2008 Production. Mini DV of the April 11, 2008 Performance (Box 1)
  - All of the Above 2008 Production digital materials, 2 files; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials UA31-07-0007-SET-0001)
    Scope and Contents
    Contains document files in MS Word format.
  - All of the Above 2013 Production: Script and Program (copy) (Box 1)
  - All of the Above Production Scripts, 2014-2015 (Box 1)
  - All of the Above 2016 Production: Script and Program (Box 1)
  - All of the Above Production Program and Script, 2017 (Box 1)
  - All of the Above Production Program and Script, 2018 (Box 1)
  - All of the Above 2019 Production digital materials, 80 files; approximatley 9 gigabytes. (Digital-materials UA31-07-0007-SET-0001)
    Includes still image files (JPEG format), video files (MP4 format), and document files (MS Word and PDF formats).
  - All of the Above 2020 Production digital materials, 21 files; approximately 4 gigabytes. (Digital-materials UA31-07-0007-SET-0001)
    Includes video files in MP4 foratm, as well as document files in MS Word and PDF formats.